Indiana University Folklore Institute Material Culture papers, 1953-1984, bulk 1960-1981 C614
Indiana University Archives
- Student Papers (Box 1)
  - M/C 73/81 Tutterow, Barth. "No pain, no grief, no anxious fear can reach the peaceful sleepers here" (North America, U.S., Indiana - Tombstones, Design), F220, Coelho, Date Unknown (Box 4)
  - M/C 73/82 Logan, James. No Title (North America, U.S., Indiana - Architecture, Roofs, Shingle), F101, Instructor Unknown, Date Unknown (Box 4)
  - M/C 73/83 Pasanen, Linda. No Title (North America, U.S., Michigan - Architecture, Log, House, Quilt), Class # Unknown, Instructor Unknown, Date Unknown (Box 4)
  - M/C 73/84 Atkerson, Kay. "The Good Times" (North America, U.S., Indiana - Occupation, Farming), F220, Rusty Marshall (TA?) (Professor Glassie?), Date Unknown (Box 4)
  - M/C 73/85 Meekins, John O. "An 18th Century Shoemaker" (North America, U.S., Ohio - Occupation, Cobbler, Shoes), Class # Unknown, Dr. Warren Roberts, April 1973 (Box 4)
  - M/C 73/86 Waclawek, Nancy. "Construction Styles of Dulcimers" (Keith Craddock - musician/craftsman, Mrs. Robert Penrod - housewife, North America, U.S., Indiana - Craft, Dulcimer, Construction), F220, Carol Edwards, November 30, 1973 (Box 4)
  - M/C 73/87 Potter, Jeanne. "The Art of Butter Churning" (North America, U.S., Indiana - Craft, Food, Butter Churning), F220, Glassie, Fall 1973 (Box 4)
  - M/C 73/88 Langlois, Janet. "An Apple a Day: Apple Dolls and Apple-Doll Craftswomen" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Colorado, Appalachia, Pennsylvania - Craft, Doll, Apple), F721, Dr. Warren Roberts, April 18, 1972 (Box 4)
  - M/C 73/89 Wong, Randall. "A Study of Folk Toys of the Southern Highlands" North American, U.S., West Virginia and Appalachia - Crafts, Toys), F721, Instructor Unknown, April 27, 1972 (Box 4)
  - M/C 73/90 Jens Lund. "Wood Graining as Done by a Professional Painter" (Europe, Denmark - Craft, Woodgraining), F721, Instructor Unknown, May 4, 1973 (Box 4)
  - M/C 73/91 Pulaski, John. "The Appalachian Dulcimer" (North America, U.S., Indiana - Craft, Dulcimer, Designs), F721, Dr. Warren Roberts, May 4, 1973 (Box 4)
  - M/C 73/92 Pomatto, Claudia. "Basketry as a Tradition," F220, Bill McNeil, December 18, 1973 (Box 4)
  - M/C 74/1 Galloway, Bill. "The Covered Bridge in Indiana" (Janson Williams - farmer, Ann Slayton - restaurant owner, North America, U.S., Indiana - Architecture, Bridge), F220, Mr. Glassie, Spring 1974 (Box 4)
  - M/C 74/2 Miller, Donna Kay. No Title (Roy Thomas - retired, North America, U.S., Indiana - History, Park, Spring Hill Park), F220, Instructor Unknown, Spring 1974 (Box 4)
  - M/C 74/3 Olinger, Jeffrey A. "Making and Repairing Violins: A Folk Craft" (Ole Steffen Dahl – folk craftsman/violin repairman, North America, U.S., Indiana – Craft, Violin Making and Repair), F220, Jens Lund, A.I., 2nd Semester 1974 (Box 4)
  - M/C 74/4 Tungett, Ronald. "Butchering and Planting by the Almanac" (Edna Hoeltke – retired farmer and housewife, North America, U.S., Indiana – Almanac, Butchering, & Planting), F220, Lightfoot, Spring 1974 (Box 4)
  - M/C 74/5 Blades, Steven. "Epitaphs" (North America, U.S., Indiana – Tombstones & Epitaphs), F391, Mr. William E. Lightfoot, Spring 1974 (Box 4)
  - M/C 74/6 Ash, Sue Alice. "(North America, Indiana – Epitaphs), F391, Lightfoot, Spring 1974 (Box 4)
  - M/C 74/7 Long, Wanda. "Project – Hooked Rugs" (Grace Johnson – housewife, North America, U.S., Indiana – Craft, Rugs, Hooked), F391, Mr. Lightfoot, Spring 1974 (Box 4)
  - M/C 74/8 Hunter, Heidi. "Apple-head Doll Making" (Mrs. Heather Renaud - student, North America, U.S., Indiana – Craft, Dolls, Apple-head), F220, Jens Lund (T.A.), Professor Glassie, April 26, 1974 (Box 4)
  - M/C 74/9 Ellis, Mary. "Weaving in Traditional Rural Georgia" (Jane Brackett – art student, North America, U.S., Georgia – Craft, Weaving), F220, Jens Lund, Spring 1974 (Box 4)
  - M/C 74/10 Block, Dennis. "The Making of Home Brew" (Lloyd C. Block – brewer, North America, U.S., Indiana – Still, distill, Home Brew), F220, Glassie, Spring 1974 (Box 4)
  - M/C 74/11 Martin, Dave. "Wrought Iron Railing" (Millard Reeves - welder, North America, U.S., Indiana – Railings, Wrought Iron), F220, Glassie, April 26, 1974 (Box 4)
  - M/C 74/12 Conley, David J. "Horse Shoeing: A Modernized Tradition" (Mr. Jerry Clase – blacksmith, North America, U.S., Indiana – Occupation, Horseshoeing), F220, Glassie, April 26, 1974 (Box 4)
  - M/C 74/13 Stuart, Gretchen. "Old Flavors and Traditions" (Opal Hinman & Dorthy Stuart, North America, U.S., Indiana - Recipes), F220, Henry Glassie, May 3, 1974 (Box 4)
  - M/C 74/14 Hicking, Jean W. "Quilting" (Vern Evans – housewife, North America, U.S., Indiana – Quilts), F391, Lightfoot, April 9, 1974 (Box 4)
  - M/C 74/15 Hult, Nancy. "Folklore" (Denver Hodnutt – Chief, North America, U.S., Indiana – Whittling, Whistle), F391, Lightfoot, April 23, 1974 (Box 4)
  - M/C 74/16 Kelly, Tom. "Folklore Project" (Curt Stoeckelmann – contractor) North America, U.S., Indiana – Architecture, Log Cabin), F220, Lund, April 19, 1974 (Box 4)
  - M/C 74/17 Taylor, Janice. No title (Mrs. Mina Taylor – housewife, North America, U.S., Indiana – Quilts), F220, Lightfoot, Spring 1974 (Box 4)
  - M/C 74/18 Brand, Ellen. "Butchering" (Richard Grow – butcher, North America, U.S., Indiana – Craft, Butchering), F391, Mr. W. Lightfoot, April 9, 1974 (Box 4)
  - M/C 74/19 Krise, Kathryn A. "Mushroom Hunting" (Rose Marie Alexander – maid, Pat Sheridou (?) – housewife, Gary Frank Gates – student, Marcia Ann Weller – student, Anne Edwards Gates –student, Patricia Jean Parrett – student, North America, U.S., Indiana – Food, Mushroom Hunting), F220, Jens Lund (T.A.), Professor Glassie, Spring 1974 (Box 4)
  - M/C 74/20 Foster, Toni and John C. Story III. "The History of Century House" (Ella Mae Sowder – retired, Mrs. John McConnell granddaughter of house's fist owner and builder, Bill C. Brown – current owner, North America, U.S., Florida – Architecture, History, Century House), F220, Professor Glassie, Spring 1974 (Box 4)
  - M/C 74/21 Murphy, Mary Kathleen (Kathy). "Dried Apple-Head Dolls" (Mrs. Olin [Alta] Armstrong – homemaker, North America, U.S., Indiana – Craft, Dolls, Apple-head), F391, William Lightfoot, June 12, 1974 (Box 4)
  - M/C 74/22 Grubb, Mark. "The Old Stone House" (Mrs. Hurbert Brown – housewife, North America, U.S., Indiana – Architecture, House, Stone), F220, Glassie, Spring 1974 (Box 4)
  - M/C 74/23 White, Evelyn and Deborah Renjilian. "Instrument Making of the Appalacian Highlands and Southern Indiana; The Crafting of Banjos, Fiddles, and Dulcimers" (Elizabeth Peck – dulcimer maker, Samuel Stevens – banjo/fiddle maker, James [Jim] Trantham – dulcimer/banjo maker, Ollie Stephen Dahl – violin maker, Keith Craddock – instrument maker, Joe Freeman – banjo/guitar maker North America, U.S., Indiana – Craft, Banjo, Fiddle, Dulcimer), F721/F391, Spring 1974 (Box 4)
  - M/C 74/24 Panich, Nicola. "The Gusle" (North America, U.S., Indiana – Craft, Music, Gusle [Yugoslavia]), F220, Jens Lund, A.I., April 26, 1974 (Box 4)
  - M/C 74/25 Hamp, Steven. "The Wilkinson's General Store in Wallace" (North America, U.S., Indiana – Architecture & History, General Store), Class # Unknown, Instructor Unknown, April 1974 (Box 4)
  - M/C 74/26 Kahrs, Paula H. "Quilting A Family Folklore Tradition" (Edna Harrison and Bessie Harrison – housewives, North America, U.S., Kentucky – Craft, Quilting), F391, Mr. Lightfoot, July 31, 1974 (Box 4)
  - M/C 74/27 Misiniec, Judy. "Quilting" (Lesta E Hart – housewife, North America, U.S., Indiana, Kentucky – Quilts), F391, Lightfoot, July 31, 1974 (Box 5)
  - M/C 74/28 Taylor, Brenda. "The Tresslar Family Quilt" (Mrs. Boyd [Eunice] Betts – retired, North America, U.S., Indiana – Craft, Quilting), F391, Lightfoot, July 28, 1974 (Box 5)
  - M/C 74/29 Baker, Keith D. "The Art of Quilt Making" (Mary Elizabeth Marshall – housewife/nurse, North America, U.S., Indiana – Craft, Quilting), F101, Lightfoot, June 18, 1974 (Box 5)
  - M/C 74/30AN Smith, Carson. "The Rose Well House" (North America, U.S., Indiana – IU Rose Well House), F220, Professor McNeil, December 18, 1973 (Box 5)
  - M/C 74/30 BN Daniel, Diana. No Title (North America, U.S., Indiana – Epitaphs), F391, Lightfoot, Summer 1974 (Box 5)
  - M/C 74/31 Day, Shirley J. No Title (North America, U.S, Indiana - Rings, Type Exchanged), F391, Lightfoot, Spring 1974 (Box 5)
  - M/C 74/32 Tieman, Len. "The Sciscoe House," F220, Instructor Unknown, May 3, 1974 (Box 5)
  - M/C 74/33 Carper, Carol. "Rag Rugs," Class # Unknown, Instructor Unknown, April 12, 1974 (Box 5)
  - M/C 74/34 Harrell, Larry. "Squatter's Rights," F220, Dr. Henry Glassie, May 2, 1974 (Box 5)
  - M/C 74/35 Eastman, Jennifer. "Log Construction in Sawtooth Valley of Idaho," Class # Unknown, Instructor Unknown, Summer 1974 (Box 5)
  - M/C 74/36 Silberman, Lynn. "The Culture of Dolls," F220, Instructor Unknown, November 15, 1974 (Box 5)
  - M/C 74/37 Lindsey, Suzanne. "PAtchworks," F220, Carol Edwards, November 21, 1974 (Box 5)
  - M/C 75/1 Owen, Blaton. "The Robert McKee House: A Typical Southern Indiana Double-Pen House" (North America, U.S., Indiana – Architecture and History, Double-Pen House), F720, Roberts, Fall 1974 (Box 5)
  - M/C 75/2 Mannenbach, Steve. "Old Manual Woodworking Tools: Their history, use, men who used them, and where they can be found." (Northern America, U.S., Indiana – Tools, Manual, Wood-working), Class # Unknown, Dr. W. Roberts, Fall 1974 (Box 5)
  - M/C 75/3 Mannenbach, Steve. "Indiana Toymakers: Ron & Rosie Tackett" (North America, U.S., Indiana – Toys, Folk, Wood, Cloth), F721, Dr. Warren Roberts, April 22, 1975 (Box 5)
  - M/C 75/4 Manolopoulos, Ellen. "A Study of Changing Food Patterns in the Greek Community of Gary, Indiana" (North America, U.S., Indiana – Food Patterns), Class # Unknown, Instructor Unknown, April 24, 1975 (Box 5)
  - M/C 75/5 Thrine, Julie. "The Art of Traditional Cooking" (North America, U.S., Indiana – Traditional Cooking), F220, Masi, December 3, 1974 (Box 5)
  - M/C 75/6 Kish, Patricia Ann. "A Little Bit of This and A Little Bit of That…" (North America, U.S., Indiana – Cookery), F220, Jens Lund, A.I., Spring 1975 (Box 5)
  - M/C 75/7 Hess, Paul. "Homemade Applebutter" (Mrs. Nina Bliss – retired meat processor, North America, U.S., Indiana – Applebutter Making), F101, Langlois, April 21, 1975 (Box 5)
  - M/C 75/8 Thieman, Vicki. "Work Horses Still Used Today" (Eldred Kamman – store keeper, trucker, farmer, bus driver, North America, U.S., Indiana – Work Horses), F220, Glassie, March 13, 1975 (Box 5)
  - M/C 75/9 Kopanko, Cindy. "The Grandma" (Mrs. Rose Galinac, North America, U.S., Indiana – Cooking, Textiles), F220, Jens Lund, A.I., Spring 1974 (Box 5)
  - M/C 75/10 McKinney, Karen. "Poke Greens, Watercress and Preservation Methods" (William McKinney – factory worker, North America, U.S., Indiana – Food Preservation and Wild Greens), F101, Langlois, April 21, 1975 (Box 5)
  - M/C 75/11 Stevens, Susan L. "The Making of Quilt Tops as Told by Florida Stevens" (Mrs. Florida Stevens – housewife, North America, U.S., Indiana – Quilt Tops), F220, Henry Glassie, Jens Lund, A.I., April 25, 1975 (Box 5)
  - M/C 75/12 Sybesma, Rosa. "Quilting as a Craft" (Gladys Mae Sowder Abel Reid – housewife, North America, U.S., Indiana –Quilting), F220, Instructor Unknown, Spring 1973 (Box 5)
  - M/C 75/13 McGiffen, Lucy. "Quiltmaking" (Mrs. Leo Yochum – housewife, North America, U.S., Indiana – Quilting), F101, Janet Langlois, December 5, 1974 (Box 5)
  - M/C 75/14 Hendricks, Jane. "Quilting Traditions" (Mrs. Frank Mitchell and Mrs. Fred McClain– housewives, Mrs. Olive Edwards – retired cook, Avyce Hendricks –Librarian, North America, U.S., Indiana – Quilting), F391, Instructor Unknown, Fall 1974 (Box 5)
  - M/C 75/15 Wilhoite, Alicia. "Two Quilters" (Mrs. Carlos Seal – guide lamp division, Mrs. Ruble Bays – retired civil service worker, North America, U.S., Indiana – Quilting), F101, Janet Langlois, A.I., Spring 1975 (Box 5)
  - M/C 75/16 Jarman, Linda. "Going Back to Beginnings" (Mrs. Blanche Butler – homemaker, North America, U.S., Indiana – Needlework), F220, Jens Lund, A.I., April 17, 1975 (Box 5)
  - M/C 75/17 Jones, Keith J. "One Man's Experience in Strip Mining (1925-1960)" (North America, U.S., Indiana – Coal Mining), Class # Unknown, Instructor Unknown, Spring 1975 (Box 5)
  - M/C 75/18 Sue, David W. "Haymaking of Southern Indiana" (Darrell Pennington –salesman and farmer, North America, U.S., Indiana – Haymaking), F220, Henry Glassie, November 22, 1974 (Box 5)
  - M/C 75/19 Hinkle, Kevin. "How an Old Pioneer Farm Transforms the Past into the Present" (Joseph Lane – farmer and former tile-ditcher, Harley Summit – T.V. sales and service, North America, U.S., Indiana – Log Barns), F220, Glassie, April 17, 1975 (Box 5)
  - M/C 75/20 Nowak, Debra K. "Ray Flowers, Mules Retiring: End of Horse-Plow Era in Bluffton Gardens?" (Ray Flowers – farmer and plowman, North America, U.S., Indiana – Mule Farming), F220, Glassie, April 17, 1975 (Box 5)
  - M/C 75/21 Harmon, Dina. "The Art of Blacksmithing" (Bruce Harmon – retired farmer, blacksmith, & carpenter, North America, U.S., Indiana – Blacksmithing), F220, Yens Lund (?), December 1974 (Box 5)
  - M/C 75/22 Schafer, Florence. "A Blacksmith Shoeing a Horse" (Timothy Meagher (?) - blacksmith, North America, U.S., Indiana – Blacksmithing), F220, Jens Lund, A.I., Fall 1974 (Box 5)
  - M/C 75/23 Pikus, Russ. "Lobster Fishing in New England" (North America, U.S., Indiana – lobster fishing), F220, H. Glassie, J. Mase (T.A.), Spring 1975 (Box 5)
  - M/C 75/24 Rodgers, Cindy. "Mr. Maurice Bridgeway-Woodcraft" (North America, U.S., Indiana – Woodcraft), F101, Cindy Rogers, Janet Langlois, A.I., December 4, 1974 (Box 5)
  - M/C 75/25 Ancelet, Barry. "Lionel Isadore Leleux: slides" (North America, U.S., Indiana – Violin Making), F517/F786, Glassie/Degh, May 1975 (Box 5)
  - M/C 75/26 Whicker, George. "Bell Collecting" (North America, U.S., Indiana – Bells), Class # Unknown, Instructor Unknown, December 2, 1972 (Box 5)
  - M/C 75/27 Stiles, Wade. "Chester Cornett" (North America, U.S., Indiana – Chair Making), F220, Instructor Unknown, December 1, 1974 (Box 5)
  - M/C 75/28 Barnett, James L. "The Roann Rolling Mill" (North America, U.S., Indiana – water-powered flour mill), F220, Professor Henry Glassie, April 17, 1975 (Box 5)
  - M/C 75/29 Potts, Jim. "A Look Into Yesterday: The Potts' Log Cabins" (North America, U.S., Indiana – Log Cabins), F220, Henry Glassie, Mr. Jens Lund, November 27, 1974 (Box 5)
  - M/C 75/30 Martin, Dick (Richard) J. "The Round Barn" (North America, U.S., Indiana – Round Barn), Class # Unknown, Instructor Unknown, April 24, 1973 (Box 5)
  - M/C 75/31 Boyce, Kathryn. "The Sanders Family and Their Log Houses" (North America, U.S., Indiana – Log Houses), F628, Henry Glassie, March 1975 (Box 5)
  - M/C 75/32 Walker, Phillip. "Tombstone Motifs" (North America, U.S., Indiana – Tombstones) F201, Instructor Unknown, May 24, 1969 (Box 5)
  - M/C 75/33 Stitt, Carol B. "A Study of Nineteenth Century Gravestones in Dubois County, Indiana" (North America, U.S., Indiana – Tombstones), F220, Glassie, Fall 1974 (Box 5)
  - M/C 75/34 McGee, Stephen P. "Gravedigging and Funerals" (North America, U.S., Indiana – Gravedigging), F220, Glassie, Jens Lund (T.A.), April 1975 (Box 5)
  - M/C 75/35 Morris, Dean. "The Blacksmith" (North America, U.S., Indiana), F220, Dr. Lewis, 1976 (Box 5)
  - M/C 75/36 Miller, Mary Jane. "A Monroe county Log Cabin" (North America, U.S., Indiana), F220, Tomas (Tom) Adler, Summer 1975 (Box 5)
  - M/C 75/37 Mecca, Annamaria. "Limestone Carving," F220, Jens Lund, February 28, 1975 (Box 5)
  - M/C 75/38 Helish, Mike. "One Time Construction," F101, Instructor Unknown, April 10, 1975 (Box 5)
  - M/C 75/39 Hoevel, Ann. "One Room Schoolhouse of Southern Indiana," Course # Unknown, Instructor Unknown, December 4, 1975 (Box 5)
  - M/C 75/40 Goodwin, Joe. "The Repetoire of the Nineteenth Century Southern Indiana Pottery," F720, Warren Roberts, 1975 (Box 5)
  - M/C 75/41 Zabriskie. "Survey of Salt Creek Diary," F7720, Warren Roberts, 1975 (Box 5)
  - M/C 75/42 Hoevel, Ann. "The Evolution of An Inventory of Vernacular Architecture in Bean Blossom Township, Monroe County, Indiana," F532, Instructor Unknown, 1975 (Box 5)
  - M/C 75/43 Chambers, Elizabeth. "Folklife and Loal History Preliminary Report: Scotland Hotel," F721, Warren Roberts, 1975 (Box 5)
  - M/C 75/44 Owen, Blanton. "Folklore of Indiana," Course Unknown, Warren Roberts, 1975 (Box 5)
  - M/C 75/44 Vidutis, Richard. "Foodways of Southern Indiana Prior to 1875," F721, Warren Roberts, 1975 (Box 5)
  - M/C 76/1 Himelick, Tom. "The Mountain Dulcimer & Dulcimer Maker in the Midwest: Four Interviews" (North America, U.S., Indiana), F220, Tom (Thomas) Adler, August 7, 1975 (Box 5)
  - M/C 76/2 Schoolcraft, Janice. "Cooperage: what is cooperage and how has the business changed over the years?" (North America, U.S., Indiana), F220, Tom Adler, November 25, 1975 (Box 5)
  - M/C 76/3 Gafken, Steve. "Stone Head" (North America, U.S., Indiana), F220, McNeil, December 18, 1973 (Box 5)
  - M/C 76/4 Mather, Diamond. "The T.J.B. Stier Home, in Stier Park, Bloomington, Indiana" (North America, U.S., Indiana – Architecture), F220, McNeil, 1973 (Box 5)
  - M/C 76/5 Sue, David W. "Haymaking of Southern Indiana" (North America, U.S., Indiana), F220, Henry Glassie, November 22, 1974 (Box 5)
  - M/C 76/6 Barton, David and Thomas Tait. "A Survey of an 'Ancient' Structure in Brown County and Petition to the National Register" (North America, U.S., Indiana), F497, R. Adams, 1975 (Box 5)
  - M/C 76/7 Lottes, David. "Quilting: Material Folklore in Practice" (North America, U.S., Indiana), F220, Glassie, Rusty Marshal (T.A.?), Fall 1972 (Box 5)
  - M/C 76/8 Vanderwerp, Mary. "Persimmon Pudding" (North America, U.S., Indiana - Food), X248 Folk Food Traditions, Langlois & Cabulska, 1975 (Box 5)
    General
    (Analog audio cassette removed and stored separately in box 10)
  - M/C 76/9 Talaska, La Verne. "Recipe's" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Columbus), F391, Instructor Unknown, July 26, 1974 (Box 5)
  - M/C 76/10 Green, David B. "The Process of Making Lye Soap" (North America, U.S., Indiana), F101, Becker, April 29, 1976 (Box 5)
    [Lye Soap sample removed]
  - M/C 76/11 Goold, Christine Bauch. "Tunnel Mill" (North America, U.S., Indiana), F220, Jens Lund, April 20, 1976 (Box 5)
  - M/C 76/12 George, Richard. "Effects of Prohibition on Rural People: Stories of 'Wet' & a 'Dry'" (North America, U.S., Indiana), F220, Mr. Jens Lund, April 20, 1976 (Box 5)
  - M/C 76/13 Berkshire, Rhonda. "Changes in Rural Cooking" (North America, U.S., Indiana), F220, Jens Lund, 1976 (Box 5)
  - M/C 76/14 Snow, Gloria A. "Wool Spinning" (North America, U.S., Indiana), F220, Jens Lund, 1976 (Box 5)
  - M/C 76/15 Bass, Meredith. "Loss of the Walkerville Covered Bridge" (North America, U.S., Indiana), F220, Jens Lund, Spring 1976 (Box 5)
  - M/C 76/16 Speakman, Margaret. "Coal Mining in Sullivan County, Indiana" (North America, U.S., Indiana), F391, Roberts, Jens Lund (T.A.), Spring 1976 (Box 5)
  - M/C 76/17 Burch, Arnold. "Covered Bridges of Indiana" (North America, U.S., Indiana), F220, Instructor Unknown, Spring 1976 (Box 5)
  - M/C 76/18 Hill, Karen. "The Art of Quilting Through One Woman's Eyes" (North America, U.S., Indiana), F220, Lewis, 1976 (Box 5)
  - M/C 76/19 Ambs, Michael L. "Preston House" (North America, U.S., Indiana), F391, Jens Lund, April 21, 1976 (Box 5)
  - M/C 76/20 Keller, Dennis. "Home-Butchering" (North America, U.S., Indiana), F220, Jens Lund, 1976 (Box 5)
  - M/C 76/21 Martin, Andy. "A Day with Burnman Cox" (North America, U.S., Indiana), F220, Jens Lund, April 11, 1976 (Box 5)
  - M/C 76/22 Dyer, David M. "Salve Hideaway" (North America, U.S., Indiana), F220, Jens Lund, 1976 (Box 5)
  - M/C 76/23 Terri Poff. "The Appalachian Dulcimer" (North America, U.S., Appalachia), F220, Instructor Unknown, November 22, 1974 (Box 5)
  - M/C 76/24 Bunch, John B. "A Photographic Survey of the Distribution and Variations of 'Double-Pen Extended' Houses in Bloomington, Indiana" (North America, U.S., Indiana), F720, Dr. Roberts, Fall 1972 (Box 5)
  - M/C 76/25 Barr, Betsy. "Hungarian Breadmaking" (Eastern Europe, Hungary), F220, Howard Marshall, December 1972 (Box 5)
  - M/C 76//26 Bucha, Joe. "Cabinetmaker" (North America, U.S., Indiana), F220, Lewis, 1975 (Box 5)
  - M/C 76/27 Bentley, Kipp. "Bread" (North America, U.S., Indiana), F220, Lewis, Fall 1975 (Box 5)
  - M/C 76/28 Wood, Martin. "Quilting" (North America, U.S., Indiana), F391, Jens Lund, 1975 (Box 5)
  - M/C 76/29 Leeper, Kay. "Quilt-making" (North America, U.S., Indiana), F391, Jens Lund, December 4, 1975 (Box 5)
  - M/C 76/30 Rampley, Robert. "Paul Rampley's Wheelbarrow" (North America, U.S., Indiana), F220, Tom Adler, August 7, 1975 (Box 5)
  - M/C 76/31 Hirsch, Dan. "Traditional Jewish Pastries, Cakes, Cookies, and Desserts" (North America, U.S., Indiana), F220, Instructor Unknown., Fall 1975 (Box 5)
  - M/C 76/32 Frankovich, John. "Traditional Slovak & Croatian Recipes" (European, Clovak/Croatian), F220, Lewis, Fall 1975 (Box 5)
  - M/C 76/34 Dinkins, Philip T. "Stonehead-An Analysis" (North America, U.S., Indiana), F220, Lewis, Spring 1976 (Box 5)
  - M/C 76/35 Champlin, Lorene. "Vern Champlin: Water Witcher" (North America, U.S., Indiana), F101, El Shamy, December 4, 1976 (Box 5)
  - M/C 76/36 Hunter, Greg. "The History of Houses Over One Hundred Years Old." (North America, U.S., Indiana), F391, Dr. Roberts, 1976 (Box 5)
  - M/C 76/37 Ellis, Donna. "Quilts in American Society" (North America, U.S., Indiana), F220, Spring 1976 (Box 5)
  - M/C 76/38 East, Richard. "Folk Architecture" (North America, U.S., Indiana), F391, Dr. Roberts, Spring 1976 (Box 5)
  - M/C 76/39 Moore, Barbara. "God's Acre." (North America, U.S., Indiana), F391, Jens Lund, December 4, 1975 (Box 5)
  - M/C 76/40 Beall, Dwight A. "Water Witching or Dowsing" (North America, U.S., Indiana), F391, Jens Lund, 1975 (Box 5)
  - M/C 76/41 Gault, Robert Leslie. "Water Witching" (North America, U.S., Indiana), F220, Instructor Unknown, 1976 (Box 5)
  - M/C 76/42 Pyle, Michael Jay. "Threshing: A Process and an Experience" (North America, U.S., Indiana), F220, Instructor Unknown, April 19, 1974 (Box 5)
  - M/C 76/43 Bartz, Doug. "Looking Through Stained Glass" (North America, U.S., Indiana), F220, Instructor Unknown, Fall 1975 (Box 5)
  - M/C 76/44 Hallett, Jennifer. "Tuesday Quilters of Brownsburg, Indiana" (North America, U.S., Indiana), F220, Instructor Unknown, Fall 1975 (Box 5)
  - M/C 76/45 Hovey, Donna. "Dollhouse: Past and Present" (North America, U.S., New York, Indiana), F220, Instructor Unknown, Spring 1976 (Box 5)
  - M/C 76/46 Solon, Karen. "Greek Cooking," F220, Instructor Unknown, Spring 1976 (Box 5)
  - M/C 76/47 Lampert, Joseph. "Covered Bridges of Parke County, Indiana" (North America, U.S., Indiana), F220, Spring 1976 (Box 5)
  - M/C 76/48 Ingram, Scott. "Draper Cabin" (North America, U.S., Indiana), F220, April 21, 1976 (Box 5)
  - M/C 76/49 White, Roxanne. "The Divining Rod" (North America, U.S. - Water Witching), Class # Unknown, Instructor Unknown (?)., 1954 (Box 5)
  - M/C 76/50 Carter, Thomas. "Stone Buildings in Franklin County, Indiana: A Preliminary Study of Butler and Ray Townships," Course Unknown, Warren Roberts, 1976 (Box 5)
  - M/C 76/51 Miller, Mary. "Fibers, Spinning, and Dyeing," F391, Warren Roberts, 1976 (Box 5)
  - M/C 76/52 Carter, Thomas. "All Work and No Play, Little Money, So They Say," Course Unknown, Warren Roberts, 1976 (Box 5)
  - M/C 77/1 Archbold, Annelen. "The Rose Homestead." (North America, U.S., Kentucky), F720, Dr. Roberts, December 13, 1974 (Box 5)